好了。你做完了。现在看看我的解决方法。因此
All right. You're done. Let's take a look at my solution. All right. So, here's
这里是我们的addlocation的函数。locationSetting, cityName,
what our addLocation function looks like, locationSetting, cityName,
latitude和longitude。就像在我们contentprovider
latitude and longitude. Just like in our content
测试中，我们能使用getContentResolver去查询
provider test, we can use getContentResolver to query
基于内容的URI。记住
based upon the content URI. Remember that the
默认，location元组CONTENT_URI传递全部的
default location entry CONTENT_URI passes all of the
参数到数据库中。因此我们能够简单的
parameters into the database. So we can easily
构建一个查询，其中包含位置的设置，去看看是否
construct a query containing the location setting to see if
它在数据库中。如果不在，那么查询
it's in the database yet. If it's not, then the query
将返回一个空集，并且我们应该插入新的
will return an empty set and we should insert the new
city name, location setting, latitude 和 longitude 到数据库中。
city name, location setting, latitude, and longitude into the database together.